{
    "subject": "resource/Ferrari",
    "predicate": "http://purl.org/dc/terms/subject",
    "object": "resource/Category:Sports_car_manufacturers",
    "human_readable": "The subject of Ferrari is sports car manufacturers.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.623313844203949,
            "question": "Does Ferrari manufacture cars?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5593041181564331,
            "question": "Is Ferrari a well-known car manufacturer globally?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5176458954811096,
            "question": "What kind of cars are made by Ferrari?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4780011773109436,
            "question": "What type of company is Ferrari?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.42095768451690674,
            "question": "What is Ferrari's main product?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3123711347579956,
            "question": "Ferrari is known for producing what?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.27979591488838196,
            "question": "Ferrari is a popular brand among what type of people?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2766742706298828,
            "question": "What makes Ferrari cars unique?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.10057209432125092,
            "question": "Is Ferrari an Italian company?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.019228758290410042,
            "question": "Are Ferraris considered luxury vehicles?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The subject of Ferrari is sports car manufacturers.",
            "html": "dbpedia_3191_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Ferrari an Italian company?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3191_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What makes Ferrari cars unique?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3191_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Ferrari is a popular brand among what type of people?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3191_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3191_115.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3191_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3191_134.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3191_137.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3191_145.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3191_153.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3191_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3191_52.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3191_56.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3191_59.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information about Ferrari as a renowned sports car manufacturer, which supports the statement that the subject of Ferrari is related to sports car manufacturers."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}